Yaroslav Kikvadze Python Developer

Enthusiastic 3th grade student eager to contribute to team success through hard work, attention to detail and excellent organization skills. Clear understanding of Python zen and REST concept and training in web frameworks.

I've been learning stack of technologies for web development since 2019. Motivated to learn, grow and excel in Web Industry.



CONTACT

Address

Kyiv, Ukraine

Phone number

+380961063678

E-mail

kikvadze.yaroslav@lll.kpi.ua

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/yar-kik/

GitHub

https://github.com/yar-kik

SKILLS

Frontend

HTML, CSS, JS, ¡Query, React.js

Backend

Python, Flask/Django, SQL, noSQL, REST API, Celery

Other

Docker, Linux, Git, Unit testing, CI/CD

EDUCATION

National Technical University of Ukraine «Kyiv Polytechnic Institute»

Bachelor's degree, Biomedical engineering 2018 – 2022

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian Russian English

EXPERIENCE

Flask Bookshop, 2021-04 – 2021-06

- Created a RESTful API application using Flask. JWT token was used for authentication and role-based access.
- PostgreSQL was used as a database, Redis was used for caching and task queue.
- Celery was used for asynchronous tasks such as sending email. Elasticsearch was used for searching query.
- Development also required Docker, writing unit-tests and Travis CI.
- Production version of application uses Gunicorn and NGINX.

Django Blog, 2020-07 – 2020-12

- PostgreSQL was used as a database.
- Django-template was used for SSR, jQuery was used for AJAX calls.
- Added Docker, Travis, logging and unittests.
- Added role-based access.
- Production version of application uses Gunicorn and NGINX

INTERESTS

Computer Games Movies Programming